Guide to the John F. Kennedy assassination conspiracy collection, [ca. 1963-2012]
Kennedy, John F., assassination conspiracy collection.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
John F. Kennedy assassination conspiracy collection, [ca. 1963-2012]
8086
Paniccioli, Ernie,
ca. 6 cubic feet.
Newspapers, Clippings, Manuscripts, Research material, Publications, Printed Material, Films, Videos
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Reports, magazines, newspaper clippings, books, and videos containing analysis of the assassination of President John. F. Kennedy, with emphasis on conspiracy theories about the event.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Reports, magazines, newspaper clippings, books, and videos containing analysis of the assassination of President John. F. Kennedy, with emphasis on conspiracy theories about the event.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Paniccioli, Ernie,; Kennedy, John F. (John Fitzgerald), 1917-1963 -- Assassination.; Kennedy, John F. (John Fitzgerald), 1917-1963 -- Death and burial.; Kennedy, John F. (John Fitzgerald), 1917-1963 -- Autopsy.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
SERIES LIST
Series I. Magazines and Newspapers
Box 1
Series II. Manuscripts
Series III. Research and Clippings
Series IV. Audio and Visual Materials
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Magazines and Newspapers
  - "Life" Magazines about JFK, 1963-2003 (Box 1)
  - "Caroline's Doll Book", 1962 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - "The Post", 1963, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - "Look" magazine, 1967, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - "Free Press", 1978 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - "Globe" paper, two copies, December 31, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - "Daily News Magazine", May 21, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - "US News and World Report", October 10, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - "Covert Action: Information Bulletin", 1983-1986 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - "Newsweek", 1993, December 1963 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - "The History Channel Magazine", 2007 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - "US News and World Report", 1992, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - "Ramparts", November 1966 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - "The Miami Herald", November 1963 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - "Probable Cause", November 1993, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - "The Dallas Times Herald", November 22, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - "JFK Lancer", 1998 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - "The Red Diaries", 1997 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - "Time", 1964, 1988, 1991, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - "Steamshovel Press", 1992-1996 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - "Esquire", November 1991 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - "Revolutionary Comics: Who Killed JFK?", 1993 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - "The New Yorker", April 10, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - "People Weekly", 1988 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - "Dallas Conspiracy", 1994 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - "Probe", 1997-2000 (Box 4, Folder 6-7)
  - "Mother Jones", August 1979 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - "Kennedy Chronicle" (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - "Texas Monthly", December 1991 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - "GQ", 1992 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - "The Men Behind the Guns", 1975 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - "Skeptic", 1975 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - "Paranoia", 1994 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - "Oswald" The Secret Files", 1992 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - "Weird", 1997 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - "High Times", 1991 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - "Daily News", November 23, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Series II. Manuscripts
  - The "JFK" Reader (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Denial, Volumes 1 and 2 (Box 3, Folder 12-13)
  - The Rather Narrative, by Monte Evans (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Inside the JFK Conspiracy, by Dan H. Christian (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - For the Defense: Case against Case Closed, by Connie Kritzberg, Shirley Lester (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Oswald's Closes Friend: the George de Mohrenschildt Story, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - The Sixth Floor Museum packet (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Deep Politics II: Essays on Oswald, Mexico, and Cuba, by Peter Dale Scott, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Possible Discovery of an Automobile Used in the JFK Conspiracy, by Richard Bartholomew, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Eye Witness, by Ed Hoffman and Ron Friedrich, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - The JFK Assassination Timeline Chart, by Bruce Campbell Adamson, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Matrix III, by Vladamar Valerian. 2 parts. (Box 3, Folder 23-24)
  - Nomenclature of an Assassination Cabal, by William Torbitt (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Questions on the JFK Assassination, by Bertrand Russell, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - The Fourth Tramp, by Ray and Mary La Fontaine, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Cosmic Patriot Files, by "The Committee of 12 to Save the Earth" (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Dr. Guinn, Neutron Activation Analysis, and the Single Bullet Theory, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Compelling Evidence, by Michael Griffith, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Larry Flynt Kills JFK Assassination Article; Yet offers $1,000,000 Reward, by Bruce Campbell Adamson, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - When They Kill A President, by Roger Craig, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Mary, Ferrie and the Monkey Virus, by Edward T. Haslam (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - JFK: The Medical Evidence Reference, by Vincent Michael Palamara, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Oswald In New Orleans, by Harold Weisberg (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Series III. Research and Clippings
  - Book lists (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Miscellaneous research papers (Box 4, Folder 28-29)
  - Scrapbook v. 1 Clippings (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Scrapbook v. 2 clippings, mainly about Oswald (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Scrapbook v. 3 clippings about affairs, Oswald and Jackie (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook v. 4 clippings (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Scrapbook v. 5 clippings (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Scrapbook v. 6 clippings (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Scrapbook v. 7 clippings (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Scrapbook miscellaneous clippings (Box 5, Folder 6-7)
- Series IV. Audio and Visual Material
  - Geraldo Show, 1991; V-6694 (Box 5)
  - Kwitney Report, Secret Health, 1988, 1993; V-6695 (Box 5)
  - The Men Who Killed Kennedy, 1992; V-6696 (Box 5)
  - Jack Anderson, 1988; V-6697 (Box 5)
  - Geraldo Show, 1991; V-6698 (Box 5)
  - Mrs. Lee Harvey Oswald, 1993; V-6699 (Box 5)
  - Lee Harvey Oswald on Trial (Geraldo Rivera), 1988; V-6700 (Box 5)
  - Jail Bush and Nixon for the Murder JFK, V-6701 (Box 5)
  - Beyond JFK: The Question of Conspiracy, V-6702 (Box 5)
  - Reasonable Doubt: The Single Bullet Theory, V-6703 (Box 5)
  - Declassified: The Plot to Kill the President, V-6704 (Box 5)
  - Who Didn't Kill...JFK, V-6705 (Box 5)
  - Ruby, V-6706 (Box 5)
  - Oliver Stone on Nightline "JFK", 1991; V-6707 (Box 5)
  - Men Who Killed Kennedy "Coup D'Etat", V-6708 (Box 5)
  - NOVA-Who Shot President Kennedy?; JFK Confession, 1990; V-6709 (Box 5)
  - Image of an Assassination: A New Look at the Zapruder Film, V-6710 (Box 5)
  - The JFK Conspiracy, V-6711 (Box 5)
  - Oswald Autopsy and Exhumation, V-6712 (Box 5)
  - JFK, V-6713 (Box 2)
  - Arts and Entertainment: JFK Assassination, V-6714 (Box 2)
  - Kennedy Scandals, V-6715 (Box 2)
  - JFK: The Case for Conspiracy, V-6716 (Box 2)
  - The Murder of JFK: Confession of an Assassin, V-6717 (Box 2)
  - The Killing of President Kennedy, V-6718 (Box 2)
  - The Many Faces of Lee Harvey Oswald, V-6719 (Box 2)
  - The Assassination of JFK, V-6720 (Box 2)
  - Best Evidence: The Research Video, V-6721 (Box 2)
  - The JFK Assassination: The Jim Garrison Tapes, V-6722 (Box 2)
  - The Men Who Killed Kennedy: The Truth Shall Make You Free, V-6723 (Box 2)
  - JFK: The Case for Conspiracy, V-6724 (Box 2)
  - The JFK Conspiracy, V-6725 (Box 2)
  - The Plot to Kill JFK, V-6726 (Box 2)
  - The Trial of Lee Harvey Oswald, V-6727 (Box 2)
  - Who Killed JFK? Facts, Not Fiction, V-6728 (Box 2)
  - American Expose: Jack Anderson "Who Murdered JFK", 1988; 887 (Box 2)
  - Dan Rather on the Trilateral Comm.; Who Killed JFK? Bryant Gumbel, 1995; 888 (Box 2)
  - JFK Current Affair; Marina Oswald, 1990; 889 (Box 2)
  - JFK: Executive Action, 890 (Box 2)
  - KGB-JFK Files; Jack Anderson, 1988; 891 (Box 2)
  - Current Affair: Mystery Tramps; James Files JFK Confession; JFK story on Twilight Zone; Original JFK News Reports, 1992; 892 (Box 2)
  - JFK: The Investigations, 1995; 893 (Box 2)
  - Frontline, "Who Was Oswald?", 1993; 894-895 (Box 2)
  - JFK Final Analysis: James Earl Jones, 1992; 896 (Box 2)
  - JFK Assassination, A and E, 897 (Box 2)
  - Marina Oswald on Oprah; JFK: Dan Rather, 1996; 898 (Box 2)
  - JFK: Now It Can Be Told, 1992; 899 (Box 2)
  - JFK, Hoffa and the Mob; Dr. Chrenshaw, 1991; 900 (Box 2)
  - Image of an Assassination; A New Look at the Zapruder Film, 901 (Box 2)
- Series V. Books
  - Coincidence or Conspiracy?, 1977. (Box 6)
  - Allen, Gary. The Rockefeller File, 1976. (Box 6)
  - Anson, Robert Sam. "They've Killed the President!": The Search for the Murderers of John F. Kennedy, 1975. (Box 6)
  - Blakey, G. Robert. Fatal Hour, 1992. (Box 2)
  - Bloomgarden, Henry S. The Gun, 1976. (Box 6)
  - Blumenthal, Sid. Government by Gunplay, 1976. (Box 6)
  - Brown, Ray "Tex" and Don Lasseter. Broken Silence, 1966. (Box 2)
  - Brown, Walt. The JFK Assassination Quiz Book, signed copy, 1995. (Box 2)
  - Condon, Richard. Winter Kills, 1975. (Box 6)
  - Craig, John R. and Philip A. Rogers. The Man on the Grassy Knoll, 1992. (Box 6)
  - Crenshaw, Charles A. JFK Conspiracy of Silence, 1992. (Box 2)
  - Davis, John H. Mafia Kingfish, 1989. (Box 6)
  - Davis, John H. The Kennedy Contract, 1993. (Box 2)
  - Delillo, Don. Libra, 1989. (Box 6)
  - Duffy, James R. Conspiracy: Who Killed JFK?, 1992. (Box 6)
  - Epstein, Edward Jay. Inquest, 1966. (Box 6)
  - Epstein, Edward Jay. Legend, 1978. (Box 2)
  - Freed, Donald. The Killing of RFK, 1975. (Box 6)
  - Freed, Donald and Mark Lane. Executive Action, 1973. (Box 6)
  - Fox, Sylvan. The Unanswered Questions about President Kennedy's Assassination, 1965. (Box 2)
  - Garrison, Jim. On the Trail of the Assassins, 1988. (Box 6)
  - Garrison, Jim. A Heritage of Stone, 1970. (Box 2)
  - Groden, Robert J. and Harrison Edward Livingstone. High Treason, 1990. (Box 6)
  - Hartogs, Renatus and Lucy Freeman. The Two Assassins, 1976. (Box 6)
  - Hirsch, Phil. The Kennedy War Heroes, 1962. (Box 6)
  - Kantor, Seth. The Ruby Coverup, 1978. (Box 2)
  - Lane, Mark. Rush to Judgment, 1975. (Box 6)
  - Mailer, Norman. The JFK Assassination: The Facts and the Theories, 1992. (Box 6)
  - Manchester, William. The Death of a President, 1967. (Box 2)
  - Marchetti, Victor and John D. Marks. CIA and the Cult of Intelligence,1974. (Box 2)
  - Marrs, Jim. Oswald's Confession, 1998. (Box 6)
  - McDonald, Hugh and Robin Moore. LBJ and the JFK Conspiracy, 1978. (Box 2)
  - McDonald, Hugh. Appointment in Dallas: The Final Solution to the Assassination of JFK, 1975. (Box 2)
  - McMillan, Priscilla Johnson. Marina and Lee, 1978. (Box 6)
  - Meagher, Sylvia. Accessories After the Fact, 1976. (Box 6)
  - Model, F. Peter and Robert Groden. JFK: The Case for Conspiracy, 1976. (Box 2)
  - Morrow, Robert D. Betrayal, 1976. (Box 6)
  - Newman, John. Oswald aand the CIA, 2008. (Box 6)
  - The New York Times. The Witnesses, 1964. (Box 6)
  - O'Toole, George. The Assassination Tapes, 1977. (Box 6)
  - Oglesby, Carl. Who Killed JFK?, 1992. (Box 2)
  - Phelps, Eric Jon. Vatican Assassins, 2001. (Box 6)
  - Popkin, Richard H. The Second Oswald, 1966. (Box 2)
  - Russell, Brian and Charles E. Sellier, Jr. Conspiracy to Kill a President, 1982. (Box 6)
  - Salisbury, Harrison and The New York Times. Report of the Warren Commission on the Assassination of President Kennedy, 1964 (Box 6)
  - Scheim, David E. Contract on American: The Mafia Murder of President John F. Kennedy, 1988. (Box 6)
  - Select Committee on Assassins. The Final Assassinations Report, 1979. (Box 2)
  - Sloan, Bill. The Other Assassin,1992, signed copy. (Box 6)
  - Southwell, David and Sean Twist. Conspiracy Files, 1999. (Box 6)
  - Speriglio, Milo. The Marilyn Conspiracy, 1986. (Box 2)
  - Thompson, Josiah. Six Seconds in Dallas: Irrefutable Evidence that Oswald Could Not Have Killed JFK Alone. (Box 6)
  - Tregaskis, Richard. John F. Kennedy: War Hero, 1962. (Box 6)
  - Vankin, Jonathan. Conspiracies, Coverups and Crimes, 1992. (Box 2)
  - Vergith, Theodore S. The Murderous Illusion: An Alternative Reconstruction of the JFK Assassination, 2000. (Box 6)
  - Weberman, Alan J. and Michael Canfield. Coup D'Etat in America, 1992. (Box 6)
  - Wecht, Cyril. Cause of Death, 1994. (Box 2)
  - Weisberg, Harold. John F. Kennedy Assassination: Post Mortem, 1976. (Box 6)
  - Weisberg, Harold. Whitewash IV: JFK Assassination Transcript, 1964. (Box 6)
  - Weisberg, Harold. Whitewash II: The FBI Secret Service Coverup, 1966. (Box 6)
  - Weisberg, Harold. Photographic Whitewash: Suppressed Kennedy Assassination Pictures, 1976. (Box 6)
  - Weisberg, Harold. Whitewash: The Report on the Warren Report,1966. (Box 6)
  - Zirbel, Craig. The Texas Connection, 1991. (Box 6)